Barbara Oliveira

Cootehill, County Cavan, Ireland

barbarahagi3@icloud.com

linkedin.com/in/barbara-oliveira-713099247

Summary

I am a twenty year old girl who is always looking to learn new things and evolve as a person. My main achievements were:

- I learned to communicate in English by myself when I was 14 years old.
- Develop a social project focused on technology at age 17.
- Learning front-end skills by myself at age 20.

I'm looking to join a company where I can develop my programming skills (front end).

Able to solve problems and learn fast (self-taught).

Able to work in a team or alone with a positive attitude.

If I could describe myself in 3 words it would be: Resilient, Initiative and Proactive.

I'm always interested in hearing from former colleagues, managers, or just interesting professionals, so feel free to contact me if you'd like to connect.

Experience

Graphic Designer

Hagge Store

May 2022 - Jul 2022 (3 months)

During two months I helped in the development of a sales website, sharing my graphic skills to develop product photos, logo and all graphic and creative material for the website.

Store Cashier

BBB multimarcas

Oct 2020 - Jan 2021 (4 months)

During the period I worked at the bbb I was able to improve my focus, logical thinking and communication with the client. A part of our work was to memorize the code of each group of products so that we could make the sum of the customer's purchase.



Nov 2018 - Apr 2020 (1 year 6 months)

I started my work journey at the age of 16 when I passed an intern competition at the Basic Sanitation company in the state of São Paulo. There I worked in administrative sectors and also in the telephone sector. I learned to develop my communication skills, teamwork, focus and also to work with spreadsheets.

Education



Rocketseat

Computer Programming
Jul 2022 - Oct 2022



Rocketseat

Learning the concepts of: fundamentals of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, SQL and more.

Prime Cursos

Business Administration and Management, General

Prime cursos

Digital marketing

escola estadual professora eulalia malta

High School Diploma

ີບ Udemy

Skills

Node.js • GitHub • Git • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 • JavaScript • Teller Operations • Cashiering • Design • Memorization

Honors & Awards

Sexta Feita

2022

First place in a social technology project in the city of Embu das Artes.